holeinthedonut.com 2013-06-03

# Disclosure, Privacy Policy | Hole In The Donut Cultural Travel

**0** Flares Twitter 0 Facebook 0 StumbleUpon 0 Google+ 0 Pin It Share 0 [](http://pinterest.com/pin/create/button/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fholeinthedonut.com%2Fdisclosure%2F&media=http://holeinthedonut.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/12/disclosure-badge.jpg) LinkedIn 0 **0** Flares ×

**DISCLOSURE:**

Hole In The Donut is a personal blog written and edited by Barbara Ann Weibel. For questions about this blog, please contact me at donutmaster (at) holeinthedonut (dot) com.

I disclose

This blog accepts paid advertising and sponsorships, which are clearly disclosed and identified as such.

I am not compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics (sometimes referred to as pay-per-post). However I do participate in press trips and familiarization (fam) trips hosted by Convention and Visitor Bureaus and/or public relations firms representing destinations, which usually provide free accommodations, food, transportation, and other travel related services. I also regularly receive free entrance to tourist attractions and other travel related entities.

If I have received a complementary product or service, or a discount on anything I write about, I will always disclose this information. In addition, I’ll always give my honest opinion about any product or service I write about, regardless of whether or not I paid for it. The receipt and acceptance of complimentary items/services received will never influence the content, topics, or posts in this blog.

The views and opinions expressed on this blog are mine and mine alone. If I claim or appear to be an expert on a certain topic or product or service area, I will only endorse products or services that I believe, based on my expertise, are worthy of such endorsement. Any product claim, statistic, quote, or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer or provider.

This blog does contain content which might present a conflict of interest. This content will always be identified.

This disclosure policy is valid from 23 December 2009

**PRIVACY POLICY:**

Any personal information you provide, including your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Hole In The Donut.

Hole In The Donut will never ask for your Credit Card details for any reason. In the event that Hole In The Donut begins to sell products or services in the future, sales will be handled by a third party service provider.

Hole In The Donut is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information. Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Hole In The Donut to recognize you each time you visit this site (customization etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Hole In The Donut does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

In order to test the usability of the Hole In The Donut’s design and layout, software may be used which captures the mouse clicks and movements of visitors.  While the visitor’s IP address may be available through these programs, it is not used for any reason, nor is any more specific, identifying information provided.

Hole In The Donut cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Hole In The Donut have separate and independent data and privacy practices, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. ****

**0** Flares Twitter 0 Facebook 0 StumbleUpon 0 Google+ 0 Pin It Share 0 [](http://pinterest.com/pin/create/button/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fholeinthedonut.com%2Fdisclosure%2F&media=http://holeinthedonut.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/12/disclosure-badge.jpg) LinkedIn 0 **0** Flares ×
